PROFILE

Born and raised in Vienna but originally from France, I grew up bilingual and speak fluent German, French, and English. Throughout my professional journey, I have gained experience in telecommunications, insurance sales, and credit control management. During my studies in biomedical engineering, I discovered a passion for programming. This newfound passion led me to explore new languages and tools, further enhancing my skills in software and web development.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Wiener Städtische Versicherung, Insurance consultant ⊗

November 2021 - May 2022 | Wien, Österreich

- Insurance Salesman Basic training completion
- Selling insurance products
- Managing customer databases
- Creating insurance analyses
- Getting insurance contracts signed by clients

- Jaguar & Land Rover customer support
- Telephone customer support
- Arranging towing and onward transport
- Estimating repair duration and technical diagnosis at the dealership
- Completion and organization of vehicle delivery

GoStudent, Credit Control Manager @

May 2022 - November 2023 | Wien, Österreich

- Maintaining learning support & optimizing cash inflows
- Contacting customers in case of payment difficulties
- Handling phone calls and processing emails
- Independent appointment scheduling and coordination
- Creating reminders and monitoring incoming payments

EDUCATION

Python Developer - Certificate, Zero to Mastery Academie January 2024 | Vienna, Austria

Victor Chesnay



deluchesnay@gmail.com | 06642468938 Pokornygasse 1A/4, 1190 Vienna, Austria 13th February 1998

https://github.com/VDeLChesS

www.linkedin.com/in/victor-chesnay-352658225

LANGUAGES

Französisch	••••
Deutsch C1 - Exam completed	••••
Englsich TOFFI	••••

SKILLS	
Adaptability/flexibility	••••
Problem-solving	••••
Customer service orientation	••••
Frontend Webdevelopment Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Boot	● ● ● ■ ©
Backend Development Datenbank Bearbeitung, MySQL, PH Framework	● ● ● ○ ○ P, Symfony

COURSES

Backend Development, CodeFactory LMS March 2024 – present | Wien, Österreich

- Datenbank Bearbeitung
- MySQL
- PHP
- AJAX
- Symfony